QUESTIONS = [
  {
    level: 1,
    question: 'How many atoms in a water molecule?',
    hint: 'H₂O',
    correct_answer: '3',
    incorrect_answers: ['1', '5', '700']
  },
  {
    level: 1,
    question: 'What is the liquid form of H₂O usually called?',
    hint: 'A refreshing beverage',
    correct_answer: 'water',
    incorrect_answers: ['ice', 'steam', 'lemonade']
  },
  {
    level: 1,
    question: 'What is water underground called?',
    hint: 'The name tells you.',
    correct_answer: 'groundwater',
    incorrect_answers: ['runoff', 'surface water', 'dish water']
  },
  {
    level: 1,
    question: 'How many hydrogen atoms are in a water molecule?',
    hint: 'H₂O',
    correct_answer: 'two',
    incorrect_answers: ['one', 'three', 'eleven']
  },
  {
    level: 1,
    question: 'What is the most common molecule on Earth?',
    hint: 'It’s a wet one.',
    correct_answer: 'H₂O',
    incorrect_answers: ['O₂', 'N₂', 'CO₂']
  },
  {
    level: 2,
    question: 'Where does the energy come from that drives the water cycle?',
    hint: 'It’s very hot.',
    correct_answer: 'the Sun',
    incorrect_answers: ['the moon', 'lightning', 'batteries']
  },
  {
    level: 2,
    question: 'What is the only substance on earth naturally found in three states of matter?',
    hint: 'It is the most common molecule on Earth.',
    correct_answer: 'H₂O',
    incorrect_answers: ['CO₂', 'Plastic', 'H₂']
  },
  {
    level: 2,
    question: 'What temperature does water freeze?',
    hint: 'Celsius temperatures are based on H₂O’s properties.',
    correct_answer: '0˚C ',
    incorrect_answers: ['32˚K', '100˚F', '0˚K']
  },
  {
    level: 2,
    question: 'H₂O on Venus is a…',
    hint: 'Venus is hot.',
    correct_answer: 'gas',
    incorrect_answers: ['solid', 'liquid', 'plasma']
  },
  {
    level: 2,
    question: 'H₂O on Mars is a…',
    hint: 'Mars is cold.',
    correct_answer: 'solid',
    incorrect_answers: ['gas', 'liquid', 'plasma']
  },
  {
    level: 3,
    question: 'When liquid H₂O becomes a gas what is the process called?',
    hint: 'Makes a vapor',
    correct_answer: 'evaporation',
    incorrect_answers: ['condensation', 'precipitation', 'floating']
  },
  {
    level: 3,
    question: 'When H₂O falls out of the sky what is this process called?',
    hint: 'Ever seen a meteorologist?',
    correct_answer: 'precipitation',
    incorrect_answers: ['evaporation', 'condensation', 'gravitation']
  },
  {
    level: 3,
    question: 'What is the freezing point of water?',
    hint: 'Between 20 and 40 degrees Farenheit',
    correct_answer: '32˚F',
    incorrect_answers: ['0˚F', '-40˚F', '12˚F']
  },
  {
    level: 3,
    question: 'H₂O is made of which two elements?',
    hint: 'It’s H₂O!!!',
    correct_answer: 'oxygen & hydrogen',
    incorrect_answers: ['oxygen & helium', 'oxygen & carbon', 'carbon & hydrogen']
  },
  {
    level: 3,
    question: 'What are rainbows caused by?',
    hint: 'Works like a prism.',
    correct_answer: 'sunlight refracted by water',
    incorrect_answers: ['the atmosphere', 'snowflakes', 'leprechauns']
  },
  {
    level: 4,
    question: 'When H₂O becomes a solid what is the process called?',
    hint: 'Snow and ice have the same molecular structure.',
    correct_answer: 'crystallization',
    incorrect_answers: ['ice making', 'snowing', 'evaporation']
  },
  {
    level: 4,
    question: 'What temperature does water boil?',
    hint: 'Celsius temperatures are based on H₂O’s properties.',
    correct_answer: '100˚C',
    incorrect_answers: ['98˚C', '32˚C', '212˚C']
  },
  {
    level: 4,
    question: 'What is it called when water molecules change from a gas to form liquid droplets?',
    hint: 'Increases in density',
    correct_answer: 'condensation',
    incorrect_answers: ['evaporation', 'precipitation', 'gravitation']
  },
  {
    level: 4,
    question: 'What is the most common element in the universe?',
    hint: '2/3 of a water molecule',
    correct_answer: 'Hydrogen',
    incorrect_answers: ['Oxygen', 'Carbon', 'Zirconium']
  },
  {
    level: 4,
    question: 'What percentage of an iceberg is under water?',
    hint: 'The vast majority.',
    correct_answer: '90%',
    incorrect_answers: ['60%', '75%', '50%']
  },
  {
    level: 5,
    question: 'What percentage of the Earth’s surface is covered with water?',
    hint: 'More than 50%',
    correct_answer: '70%',
    incorrect_answers: ['50%', '25%', '90%']
  },
  {
    level: 5,
    question: 'How long can a person live without water?',
    hint: 'There are 4 in most months.',
    correct_answer: 'approx. 1 week',
    incorrect_answers: ['approx. 3 days', 'approx. 2 weeks', 'approx. 1 month']
  },
  {
    level: 5,
    question: 'How much of the human body is composed of water?',
    hint: 'A majority',
    correct_answer: '66%',
    incorrect_answers: ['50%', '25%', '90%']
  },
  {
    level: 5,
    question: 'Which state of matter has a definite shape?',
    hint: 'What happens to uncontained liquids?',
    correct_answer: 'solid',
    incorrect_answers: ['liquid', 'gas', 'plasma']
  },
  {
    level: 5,
    question: 'Which has the highest density?',
    hint: 'Ice floats on water',
    correct_answer: 'water',
    incorrect_answers: ['ice', 'vapor', 'slush']
  },
  {
    level: 6,
    question: 'Which state of matter has the greatest volume?',
    hint: 'What spreads out the farthest?',
    correct_answer: 'gas',
    incorrect_answers: ['liquid', 'solid', 'plasma']
  },
  {
    level: 6,
    question: 'What is the boiling point of water?',
    hint: '180˚F above the freezing point.',
    correct_answer: '212˚F',
    incorrect_answers: ['100˚F', '156˚F', '278˚F']
  },
  {
    level: 6,
    question: 'What is another name for the Water Cycle?',
    hint: '"Hydro" means "water".',
    correct_answer: 'Hydrologic Cycle',
    incorrect_answers: ['Dehydration Cycle', 'Refreshment Cycle', 'Weather Cycle']
  },
  {
    level: 6,
    question: 'Which process purifies salt water for animals to drink?',
    hint: 'Gaseous process',
    correct_answer: 'evaporation',
    incorrect_answers: ['sublimation', 'condensation', 'precipitation']
  },
  {
    level: 6,
    question: 'A hydrophobic molecule…',
    hint: 'Phobic means "afraid of".',
    correct_answer: 'repells water',
    incorrect_answers: ['attracts water', 'sinks in water', 'floats on water']
  },
  {
    level: 7,
    question: 'What percentage of water on Earth is fresh water?',
    hint: 'Lower than you think',
    correct_answer: '3%',
    incorrect_answers: ['10%', '25%', '99%']
  },
  {
    level: 7,
    question: 'What percentage of the Earth’s water is in the oceans and sea?',
    hint: 'There’s a lot of water in the oceans',
    correct_answer: '97%',
    incorrect_answers: ['56%', '77.7%', '89%']
  },
  {
    level: 7,
    question: 'What percentage of fresh water on Earth is in groundwater?',
    hint: 'A lot!!',
    correct_answer: '99%',
    incorrect_answers: ['80%', '75%', '50%']
  },
  {
    level: 7,
    question: 'What is the Earth’s longest river?',
    hint: 'Think pyramids.',
    correct_answer: 'Nile',
    incorrect_answers: ['Amazon', 'Mississippi', 'Yangtze']
  },
  {
    level: 7,
    question: 'How many electrons does an H₂O molecule contain?',
    hint: 'Double digit answer',
    correct_answer: 'ten',
    incorrect_answers: ['eight', 'three', 'twelve']
  },
  {
    level: 8,
    question: 'What percentage of fresh water on Earth is in the polar icecaps and glaciers?',
    hint: 'More than you might guess',
    correct_answer: '69%',
    incorrect_answers: ['5%', '27%', '53%']
  },
  {
    level: 8,
    question: 'How many H₂O molecules can one H₂O molecule hydrogen bond with at one time?',
    hint: 'A tetrahedral relationship',
    correct_answer: 'four',
    incorrect_answers: ['three', 'two', 'one']
  },
  {
    level: 8,
    question: 'When snowflakes form, which phase change happens?',
    hint: 'It does not go through a liquid state.',
    correct_answer: 'gas to solid',
    incorrect_answers: ['liquid to solid', 'gas to liquid to solid', 'plasma to solid']
  },
  {
    level: 8,
    question: 'Why does ice float on water? Because it is…',
    hint: 'Expansive',
    correct_answer: 'less dense',
    incorrect_answers: ['more dense', 'colder', 'dryer']
  },
  {
    level: 8,
    question: 'Sleet and hail are…',
    hint: 'Made of ice',
    correct_answer: 'rain that freezes',
    incorrect_answers: ['snow that melts', 'vapor that freezes', 'frozen puppy tears']
  },
  {
    level: 9,
    question: 'What state of matter are clouds?',
    hint: 'Where do snow and rain come from?',
    correct_answer: 'all of the above',
    incorrect_answers: ['solid', 'liquid', 'gas']
  },
  {
    level: 9,
    question: 'What kind of pattern does an ice lattice form?',
    hint: '6 sided',
    correct_answer: 'hexagonal grid',
    incorrect_answers: ['octagonal grid', 'orthogonal grid', 'cubic grid']
  },
  {
    level: 9,
    question: 'What is the Earth’s largest lake (by volume)?',
    hint: 'Doesn’t sound like a lake.',
    correct_answer: 'Caspian Sea, Asia',
    incorrect_answers: ['Lake Baikal, Russia', 'Lake Victoria, Africa', 'Lake Superior, US/Canada']
  },
  {
    level: 9,
    question: 'H₂O molecules are attracted to each other through…',
    hint: 'Friendly atoms',
    correct_answer: 'hydrogen bonding',
    incorrect_answers: ['magnetism', 'covalent bonding', 'adhesion']
  },
  {
    level: 9,
    question: 'What is the average freezing point of saltwater?',
    hint: 'Just lower than fresh water.',
    correct_answer: '-2˚C',
    incorrect_answers: ['-5˚C', '-10˚C', '0˚C']
  },
  {
    level: 10,
    question: 'What is precipitation that evaporates before it reaches the Earth’s surface called?',
    hint: 'You’ve probably never heard of it.',
    correct_answer: 'Virga',
    incorrect_answers: ['snow', 'rain', 'recipiation']
  },
  {
    level: 10,
    question: 'What is it called when water molecules change from a gas directly to a solid?',
    hint: 'Snowflakes form this way.',
    correct_answer: 'deposition',
    incorrect_answers: ['sublimation', 'condensation', 'precipitation']
  },
  {
    level: 10,
    question: 'Which has properties that absorb the most warmth from the sun?',
    hint: 'Think dark. It is the least reflective.',
    correct_answer: 'sea water',
    incorrect_answers: ['icecaps', 'snow', 'waterfalls']
  },
  {
    level: 10,
    question: 'What is Earth’s most common substance?',
    hint: 'It’s makes up the Earth’s core.',
    correct_answer: 'iron',
    incorrect_answers: ['water', 'dirt', 'plastic']
  },
  {
    level: 10,
    question: 'What is the freezing point of water?',
    hint: 'Somewhere in the middle',
    correct_answer: '273˚K',
    incorrect_answers: ['395˚K', '211˚K', '165˚K']
  },
  {
    level: 10,
    question: 'What is it called when water molecules change directly from a solid to a gas?',
    hint: 'A sublime reaction.',
    correct_answer: 'sublimation',
    incorrect_answers: ['desublimation', 'condensation', 'precipitation']
  }
]
